Henle, Peter Research files 5866
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Peter Henle Research files
1971-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Henle, Peter
5866
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5722545
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5588: David L. Cole Papers 6007: U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6047: Archives Information File 6346 PUBS: Seyfarth Shaw Labor Publications
Collective bargaining; Henle, Peter
5722545
- Reverse Collective Bargaining - ILR Review, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Apr. 1973
- Tire Companies, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Akron, OH
- Firestone Tire & Rubber, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- B. F. Goodrich, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Goodyear Tire & Rubber, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Various Companies, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Detroit, MI
- General Electric, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- GM Appliance - IUE, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Dayton, OH
- GTE Sylvania - IUE, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Batavia, NY
- Goodyear Tire & Rubber, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Windsor, VT
- Jamestown, NY Companies & Buffalo, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Meat-Packing Plants in South, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Steel Companies, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Uniroyal, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Naugatuck, CT
- Collective Bargaining, Reverse, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Misc. Cases & Notes for Article